It was always a question for speculation whether the kinds of nets developed for
这总是个问题 推测被用作
recognizing handwritten digits could actually be scaled up to what vision
手写数字识别的神经网络是否可以大规模的被用作
people call a real task. That is, recognizing objects in high
人们所称的实际任务 也就是 识别物体于
resolution color images when the scene is cluttered.
高分辨率的颜色图像中 而且场景是杂乱无章时
So that you have to do things like segmentation, you have to deal with 3D
所以你不得不做一些事情 比如图像分割 处理3D
viewpoint, you have to deal with 5-foot list.
视角 处理5-foot list
Many different objects surrounding, you're not quite sure which is the intended one,
很多不同的物体在周围 你不是很确定哪一个是想要的
and so on. Since the start of this course, we've got
诸如此类 自从本课程开始 我们已经得到
some interesting new results on that. So in my first lecture, I described the
让方面一些有意思的新结论 在我第一节课中 我描述了
network developed by Alex Krizhevsky and showed that it was good at object
Alex Krizhevsky建立的网络 展示了它善于识别物体
recognition. But at that point it hadn't been
但是在那个时候它还没有被
benchmarked against the best computer vision systems,
最好的计算机视觉系统进行标准测试
Now it has. People worked on Emenise for many years,
现在有了 人们致力于研究Emenise很多年了
gradually improving their ability of these networks to recognize handwritten digits.
渐渐地提升了它们识别手写数字的能力
Many computer vision researchers thought this was a waste of time if you wanted to
很多计算机视觉研究者认为这是浪费时间 如果你想要
be able to recognize real objects in color images, because they thought the lessons
能够在有颜色的图片中识别真实的物体 因为他们认为
learned from Emnise would not generalize to that domain.
从Emnise中学到的东西无法推广到那个领域
That was a fairly reasonable thing to think.
这样想是很合理的
Here's a number of reasons why it's a much more difficult task.
这里有很多原因来解释为什么这是一个更加困难的任务
First of all, there's many, many more different kinds of objects.
首先 这里有很多很多不同的物体
Even if we only recognize a thousand classes, that's still a factor of a
尽管我们仅仅识别一千种类别 这仍然是一百的倍数
hundred. Secondly there is many more pixels even if
第二 这里有很多的像素点 尽管
we use trans sampled images that are only 256 by 256 with color pixels that's still
我们使用大量仅仅是256*256像素的图片 这仍然是
100 or 300 times of many pixels Another factor is that in real scenes you have to
100或者300倍于28*28的灰度图像 另外一个因素是在真实的场景中 你不得不
deal with the fact you've got a two dimensional image of a three dimensional
处理三维世界中的二维图片
reality so a lot of information is being lost.
这样很多信息都会丢失
And real scenes have clutter of a kind that doesn't occur in handwriting.
真实场景有杂乱的类别 可能在手写中没有出现
In handwriting you can have overlapping letters and that requires segmentation but
在手写中可能有重叠的字母 这需要分割 但是
you don't have things like occlusion of large parts of objects by opaque other
你没有东西模糊其他物体来遮挡物体的一大部分
objects. You don't have many different kinds of
你没有很多不同种类的
objects in the same scene. And you don't have a little lighting
物体 在同一场景下 你也没有一些
variations that you get in real scenes. So the question is will the same kind of
在真实场景中的光照变化 所以问题是同种
convolution neural network that proved to be so good on recognizing hand written
在手写数字识别中表现的很好的卷积神经网络
digits work for real color images In the domain of real color images we probably do
也会在真实颜色的图片中表现的很好吗 在真实颜色图片的领域我们很可能
need to wire in some prior knowledge. Because, if we try and do it in the sera
需要去结合一些先验知识 因为 如果我们努力用sera san的方法去做
san way with no knowledge wired in, putting in all the knowledge by generating
而不结合一些知识 通过
extra training examples. The computational problem is still too
产生额外的训练样本来得到知识 则计算量
large for current computers. So there was a recent competition.
对于现在的计算机来说是很大的 所以最近有一个竞赛
And it was on a data base called ImageNet. ImageNet actually has many more than a
基于ImageNet的数据库 ImageNet事实上有超过
machine images but a subset of 1.2 millimeters was chosen and the
一百万的图片 但是有120万图片的子集
classification task was to correctly label those images.
被选来做分类的任务 正确的为这些图片贴上标签
Now the images were hand labelled with a thousand different classes but this wasn't
现在这些图片被手工标签 有一千种不同的类别 但是这不
very reliable. There could be an image that has two of
太可靠 一张图片里可能有两个
those thousand different objects in it and only one of them is labeled.
在这一千种类别中出现的物体 但仅仅标记了一个
So, to make the task feasible the computer vision system is allowed to make five
所以 为了让这个任务更可行 计算机视觉系统被允许做五个预测
bets. And it's set to get it right if one of
它被认为是正确的 如果这五个之中有一个
those bets corresponds to the label that a person has given the image.
与人工给的标签一致
There's also a localization task. The reason for the localization task is
这里也有一个定位任务 理由是
that many computer vision systems use a bag of features approach.
很多计算机视觉系统使用特征袋方法
For the whole image or for say, a quadrant of the image they know what the features
对于整个图片或者四分之一图片 它们知道特征
are, but they don't know where they are. This allows them to recognize objects but
是什么 但是不知道特征在哪里 这使得它们识别物体的同时
without knowing exactly where they are. That's very unlike how people behave
但是并不知道物体究竟在哪里 这不像人类的行为
except people with a curious kind of brain damage called balance syndrome where they
除非是大脑好奇部位损伤 即平衡综合征的人
can recognize objects and not be sure where they are.
他们可以识别物体但是不确定在哪
So for the localization task you have to place a box around an object once you've
所以对于定位任务 你不得不在物体周围放一个盒子 一旦你已经
recognized it and to get it right your box must have at least a 50% overlap with the
识别到了它 然后把它放进盒子 至少与正确的盒子有50%的交集
correct box. On this task, people tried some of the
在这个任务中 人们尝试了一些
best existing computer vision methods. So, leading groups from Oxford and the
现存最好的计算机视觉方法 牛津大学的领头团队和
French National Research Labs Inria and Xerox's European Research Center and
法国国家信息与自动化研究所 和 施乐欧洲研究中心
various other universities tried this task and discovered it's very hard.
以及其他不同的大学努力 都觉得这很难
The computer vision systems typically use complicated multi-stage systems.
计算机视觉系统通常使用复杂的多级系统
The early stages of these systems are typically hand-tuned by optimizing a few
这些系统早期时通常使用手工调节来
parameters using some of the data. And, the top stage of these systems is
使用一些数据优化参数 现在这些系统是
always a learning algorithm. But they don't learn all the way through.
使用的学习算法 但是他们不能学习到所有的东西
In the way that a deep neural net does when its trained to do back propagation.
方式是深度神经网络被训练来做后向传播
They don't have end-to-end learning, where the parameters used in the early feature
他们没有端到端的学习 在早期特征检测器中使用的参数
detectors are being influenced by how useful they are for making final decision
被制定决策分类中的作用大小所影响
about classes. So here are some examples from the test
因此这里有一些测试集的样本
set to show you what the data is like. You already sow some examples in the first
来告诉你数据是怎么样的 你已经看到一些例子 在第一个课程里
lecture, but here's some more. So you can see that it's fairly obvious
但是这里还有一些 所以你可以很明显的看到
what the object is in that image, but a lot of it's missing.
图像中的物体是什么 虽然很多东西都缺失了
It doesn't have ears, it doesn't have legs.
它没有耳朵 没有腿
The predictions are the un-normalized probabilities of Alex Krizhevsky's
预测结果是在Alex Krizhevsky的深度神经网络中 没有归一化的概率
deep-neural-network. And you can see it's confident that, that
你可以看到它有十足的把握说
is a cheetah And if it's not a cheetah, it thinks it almost sudden a leopard.
这是一只猎豹 如果不是猎豹 它会认为可能是一只豹子
It also understands there's other possibilities, like a snow leopard, it's
它也给出了其他的可能性 比如一只雪豹
the wrong color for a snow leopard, or an Egyptian cat.
这不是一只雪豹的颜色 也不是埃及猫
Here's an example the other way around, here there's many objects in the image and
这是另外一个例子 这张图片中有很多物体
the object of interest is only a very small fraction of the pixels.
但是感兴趣的只占很小一部分像素
The network correctly says bullet train. But it also has other bets, like subway
神经网络正确的将它归为子弹头列车 但是他也有其他的假设 比如地铁
train or electric locomotive, which are presentable bets.
或者电力动车 这都是有可能的假设
If you look at the image, there's lots of other things that could be labeled, like
如果你看图片 有很多物体都可以被作为标签
the roof which occupies a much larger fraction of the image than the train or
比如 屋顶 占了图片很大一部分空间 比列车或者
the pillar that's supporting the roof or the pedestrian.
支撑屋顶和人行道的柱子
Or the large apartment block in the background.
或者背景部分的公寓楼
In these kinds of images you really have to be able cope with the fact that there's
在这种图片中 你不得不处理这种情况
lots of alternative targets. Last image shows a different kind of
图片中有很多可以选择地目标 最后一张图片展示了不同种类的
example where there is no background clutter.
例子 这里没有背景杂物
The object is quite well isolated, probably a picture from a catalog or
物体被很好的分离出来 可能是目录用的图片或者什么
something. And the network doesn't get it right for
神经网络第一次没有预测正确
its first bet, but it does get it in its top five bets.
但是在最可能的五个预测中
But here the network isn't confident about anything.
但是这里神经网络并不是很有把握
These are the relative probabilities, and the network correctly realizes it doesn't
他们的概率都近似 网络正确的意识到他
really know. And if you look at the other
不是真的清楚 如果你看另外左边两个的
possibilities, they're all perfectly plausible.
概率 他们都有很好的把握
If you screw your eyes up so you can't see the image too well, you can see how it
如果你眯起你的眼睛以至于你不能很好地看到图片 你就知道它为什么
might think it was a frying pan or a stethoscope.
可能认为这是一个煎锅或者听筒
So how did the systems do on this data? Here's the error rates for the computer
那么系统如何处理这些数据呢 计算机视觉系统有差错率
vision systems. One thing you'll notice is that the best
你能注意到的一件事是最好的
systems are all very similar. So the University of Tokyo managed to get
系统都很相似 所以东京大学得到了
26.1%, and here what I'm doing is just reporting the best system from each group.
26.1%的差错率 这里我只是报道每个团队最好的系统
Oxford University, which has a very good computer vision group, generally
牛津大学有很好的计算机视觉团队 通常
recognized to be possibly the best group in Europe, again got in the 26 percents
被认为是欧洲最好的团队 但是还是有26%的差错率
and the French National Research Labs in the Xerox Park Center, which are, again, a
位于施乐公园中心的法国国家信息与自动化研究所 也是
very good computer vision groups, got 27%. So you'll guess from this that it is going
一个很好的计算机视觉团队 得到了27%的差错率 所以你可以从中猜测得到
to be hard to be 26%, and if you do beat 26% you're comparable with the very best
26%是很难得的 如果能超过26%你就能与最好的
computer vision systems. So Alex Krizhevsky's neural net got
计算机视觉系统并驾齐驱了 Alex Krizhevsky的神经网络得到了
sixteen percent error. It's a huge gap.
16%的差错率 这是一个很大的飞跃
Normally, in these competitions you don't see big gaps like that.
通常 在这样的竞争中你不会看到像这么大的飞跃
So Alex Krizhevsky's network works like this.
因此Alex Krizhevsky的网络像这样工作的
It's a very deep convolutional neural net of the type pioneered by Yann Le Cun was
它是一个很深的卷积神经网络 由Yann Le Cu所创始
first used for digit recognition and then Yann later applied it to recognizing real
率先被由于数字识别 然后Yann应用它来识别真实
objects. And we're using all the lessons that we
物体 我们将用所有的
learned by Yann's group from [UNKNOWN] group and various other groups, developing
从Yann和[未知]各个不同的团队学习的课
these deep neural nets for doing real vision.
来为做真正的视觉建立深度神经网络
It has seven hidden layers, which is deeper than usual and that's not counting
它有七个隐藏层 这比 通常都深 而且没有计算
some of the max-pooling layers. The early layers are convolutional.
一些最大池化层 靠前的是卷积层
We could probably get away with using just local receptive fields, without tying any
我们很可能不需要本地感受野 不用任何
weights, if we had a much bigger computer. But by making them convolutionary, you cut
权重 如果我们有一个很强的计算机的话 但是通过使他们卷积 你减少了
down the parameters a lot, so you cut down the amount of training data you need a lot
很多参数 所以减少了很多你需要的训练数据
which cuts down the amount of computation time a lot.
这同时也减少了计算所花的时间
The last two loads were globally connected and that's where most of the parameters
最后两层总是被连接着的 这也是大多数参数所处的地方
are. I think there's about sixteen million
我想这里大约有一千六百万
parameters between each pair of those layers.
的参数介于每两层之间
What the last two layers are doing is looking for combinations of local features
最后两层所做的是寻找到本地特征的组合
that were extracted by the early layers. And obviously this commonly tourily many
这些特征是被之前的层提取出来的 显然这通常也是很多
combinations to look for. And that's why you need a lot of
组合所寻找的 这解释了为什么你需要很多
parameters there. The activation functions were rectified
参数 激活函数是修正过的
linear units in every hidden layer. These train much faster than logistic
线性单元位于每个隐藏层中 这比逻辑
units and they're more expressive. Most of the people seriously applying deep
单元训练的更快 也更加有效 大多数人都谨慎的使用深度
in your own networks to real images to the object recognition of I switch direct fi
神经网络 来从真实图片中识别物体 用我定义过的
linear units. We also used competitive normalization,
线性单元 我们也用竞争规则化
within a layer to suppress the activity of a unit, if other units that are looking
在层内抑制一个单元的活跃性 如果附近的其他的单元
nearby localities are very active. This helps a lot with variations in
十分活跃 这对于强度差异性有很大帮助
intensity. So, you might have an edge detector, which
因此 你可能有一个边缘检测器
gets somewhat active due to some fairly faint edge.
因为一些微弱的边缘而变得有些活跃
And that's pretty much irrelevant, if there is much more intense things around.
这是很不相关的 如果这附近有更多强烈的活动
There's other tricks that we used to significantly improve the generalization
这里也有很多其他的技巧 我们用来有效的提升网络的普适性
of this net. First of all, we use the trick of
首先 我们使用
enhancing the data by using transformations.
通过变换强化数据的技巧
So here's a skit for down-sampled the images in the competition to 256 by 256.
这里有一个方法用来对图片在竞争中下采样到256*256维
But instead of using those whole images Alex Krizhevsky took random 224 by 224
但相反 Alex Krizhevsky从这些图片 随机取了224*224
patches from those images. Which gave him hugely more images to train
的分块 这给他更多图片去训练
on. And helped him deal with translation and
也帮助他处理了平移和变化
variance. Even though they're convolutional nets
尽管它们是卷积网络
that's still a help. He also used left-right reflections of the
但还是有用的 它也使用了图片的左右翻转
images, which again doubled the amount of data.
这再一次加倍了数据量
He didn't use up dime reflections. Because, gravity's very important.
他没有使用角反射 因为重力是很重要的
Left right reflections don't really change what things look like much unless they're
左右翻转其实没有改变事物表面的样子 除非
things like writing. At test time, he doesn't just use one
它们是书写类的事物 在测试的时候 他没有只用一个
patch. He uses a number of different patches, the
分块 他使用了很多不同的分块
four corners, the middle, that gives him five, and then the left right reflections
四个角 中间部分 这给他了五个区域 然后是所有的左右翻转
of all those, that gives him ten. He runs all ten through the network and
这一共有十个 他在网络中用了所有的十张图片
then combines their opinions. In the top layers, where most of the
然后结合他们的观点 在顶层 大多数参数在的地方
parameters are, he uses a new regularization technique, called drop-out,
他使用了一个新的规则化方法 叫做Dropout层
which is very effective. And stops the network over fitting.
这是很有用的 帮助防止网络过拟合
That's worth several percent in his results.
这在他的结果中占了一定的比例
I'll describe drop pouch at some length in the later lecture.
我将在以后的课程中详细的描述Dropout
But for now, the basic idea of drop out is that each time you present a training
但是现在 dropout的基本想法是 在每次给出一个训练样本的时候
example, you omit half the hidden units from a layer.
你从一层中忽略一半的隐藏单元
This means that the other hidden units in that layer, the survivors, can't rely on
这意味着其他存活下来的隐含单元不能依赖
the their com rates being present. They can't learn to fix up the errors left
他们得到的总和 他们不能学会修补错误
over by the other hidden units in that layer, cuz the other hidden units might
被其他隐含层遗留下来的错误 因为其他隐含单元可能
not be there no matter be fixing up an error that doesn't exist.
被忽视了 无论是修复一个不存在的错误
So they have to become more individualist. They have to individually do useful things
所以他们不得不变得更加利己 他们不得不各自做有用的事情
but they still have to do useful things that are different from what the other
但是他们仍然不得不去做有用的事情 不同于那些留存下来的单元做的
survivors do. So drop out is stopping too much
所以dropout阻止了太多
cooperation between the hidden units. And a lot of cooperation is very good for
隐含单元之间的合作 很多合作对
fitting the training data. But if the test distribution is
拟合数据很有用 但是如果测试集的分布
significantly different, then all that cooperation causes over-fitting.
显著不同 那么所有的合作 都会造成过拟合
Alex couldn't have done this work without significant hardware, but the hardware
Alex没法不用强大的硬件来完成这个工作 但是硬件
only costs a few thousand dollars now. Alex is a very good programmer, and he
现在只需要几千美元 Alex是一个很厉害的程序员
used a very efficient implementation of convolution and neural nets on two Invidia
它使用了高效的方法实现卷积和神经单元 在两个英伟达
GTX 580 graphics processors. Each of these has over 500 fast little
GTX 580的图形处理器上 每一个都有500个快速的核
cores, which are very good at doing arithmetic and not much good at anything
它们擅长于数学运算 而不擅长于其他任务
else. The GP use are very good at doing matrix,
图形处理器很擅长于做矩阵运算
matrix multiplies. So if you stack together the vector of
矩阵乘法 所以如果你把隐含层的激励向量堆在一起
activities of a hidden layer, over many training cases, that gives you a matrix.
并基于很多训练样本 这样得到一个矩阵
And now you multiply that by matrix of weights to figure out the activities in
现在你将这个矩阵和权重矩阵相乘来得到
the next hidden layer for all those training cases.
下一隐含层的所有训练样本的激励
And if both those matrices are big, the GPU's give you a huge advantage.
如果这些矩阵都很大 GPU会有很大的优势
They give you about a factor of 30. They also have very high bandwidth to
他们给你大约30倍的速度 他们到内存间也有很高的带宽
memory, and that's needed for neural nets. Cause in neural nets you keep wanting to
这对神经网络是很需要的 因为在神经网络中你一直希望
know another weight so that you can multiply it by an activity.
得到另外一个权重 这样你可以用激励乘上它
And there's millions of these weights, so you can't keep them all in the cache.
这里有上百万的权重 因此你无法将他们保存在高速缓存中
Using all that hard brac, he could train his final network, in a week.
用所有的这些硬件优势 他可以一周内训练出最终的网络
And you could also combine results from ten, ten different patches of TestTime
你也可以把十个分块联系起来 在测试时
very quickly. So Test Time you can run it at just about
很快 所以测试时你可以用帧频来运行
the frame rate. In the future we are going to be able to
在未来我们将能够
spread this kind of network over a large number of calls.
将这种神经网络延伸到很多核心上
As calls become cheaper, people at Google are already experimenting with that.
随着核价格的降低 Google已经能用这个实验了
And if we can communicate the stakes fast enough we are going to be able to do much
而且如果我们能在状态间通讯的足够快 我们将能
bigger networks on many more calls. Google has already simulated networks with
在更多的核心上做更大的网络 Google已经模拟了
1.7 billion connections and I think that it's only going to get bigger.
17亿连接的网络 我认为这还会继续增大
As the cores get cheaper and the data sets get bigger, these big deep neural nets are
随着核心变得越来越便宜 数据集越来越大 这些深度神经网络将
gonna improve much faster than the old-fashioned computer vision systems,
比老式计算机视觉系统改进得更快
because they don't involve much hand engineering, and they can make very good
因为他们没有涉及太多的人工操作 他们可以更好地
use of huge data sets and huge amounts of computation.
使用大规模数据集和大规模运算
So the fact that we've already opened up a big gap I think means there's no looking
所以我们已经开启了一个大的突破口 我认为没有必要往回看了
back. I think from now on all the best object
我想 从现在开始所有最好的物体
recognition systems, at least of static images, will use big deep neural nets.
识别系统 至少对于一些静态图片 将会使用大的深度神经网络
There are other application domains where we've learned the same lesson so Vladimir
这里有其他的应用领域 我们可以学到同样的东西
Nee. Used a net with local fields but without
Vladimir Nee使用了一个本地区域的网络
convolution to extract roads from aerial images.
没有用卷积去从航拍照片中提取道路
These are cluttered aerial images of urban scenes.
这些事很杂乱的城市地区的航拍图
Again he uses multiple layers of rectified linear units.
他也使用了多层修正线性单元
And he takes a relatively large image patch, and predicts for the central 16x16
他使用了一张相对大的图片分块 预测了中央16*16
pixels whether each of those pixels is a piece of road or not a piece of road.
像素区域是道路的一块或者不是
The nice thing about this task is that there's a lot of label training data
比较好的事情是训练数据有很多标签
available. That's because maps tell you where the
可用 这是因为地图告诉你哪里
centre lines of roads are and roads are roughly fixed width.
是道路中心线 哪里是差不多固定的宽度
So from the vectors in the map that tell you where the centre line of the road is
地图中的向量可以告诉你道路的中心线在哪
you can estimate which pixels are probably road.
你可以估测哪些像素可能是道路
Nevertheless, the task is very hard. There's the normal kind of vision
然而 这个任务很难 这通常有一个视觉
problems: so roads are occluded by buildings because a plane isn't looking
问题 道路会被建筑物所遮挡 因为飞机不是
straight down when it takes the photograph.
垂直往下拍照的
They're occluded by trees. They're also occluded by cars that are
他们被树挡住了 也被那些
sitting on the road. The shadow effects from building, the
停在路边的车挡住 建筑物旁的阴影
major lighting changes depending on whether it's a sunny day or a cloudy day
主要的光照取决于是晴天还是阴天
for example and there's minor view point changes.
举个例子 这里有很小的视角点变化
So the plane is basically looking downwards, but in any large photo it can't
飞机基本上是朝下看的 但是在任何一个大的照片中它无法
be looking straight downwards at every pixel.
保证每一个像素点都是垂直向下看的
The worst problems in this data are the incorrect labels.
数据中最坏的问题是不正确的标签
You get incorrect labels because the maps aren't perfectly registered.
你得到错误的标签 因为地图不是完美无缺的被记录
For most purposes, you don't need a map to be registered better than a few meters.
对于大多数的目的 你不需要地图被记录精准到几米
The pixels are about one meter square in this data.
在这个数据中的一个像素大约是一平方米
And so if the registration of the map is off by three meters, you're going to get
如果地图的记录偏差超过三米 你将会得到
at least three of the labels wrong for pixels, across every road.
三个错误的标签 对每条路的像素来说
Another, severe problem, is that the people making maps have to make arbitrary
另外 一个严重的问题 人们制作地图的时候不得不武断地
decisions about what counts as a road and what counts as a laneway.
决定哪个被记为道路 哪个被记为巷道
So, in may of the maps, you look at something, and you've no idea whether
因此在大多数的地图中 你看到一些东西 你不知道怎么判断
that's gonna be considered to be a road or a lane-way.
这是被记为一条道路还是一条巷道
And so you simply don't know what label it's gonna get from the map.
因此你很容易困惑 不知道从地图中得到哪个标签
Big neural nets trained on big image patches, using millions of examples, are,
在很大图片块上训练的大规模神经网络 使用几百万个样例
I think, the only real hope for doing a good job at this task.
我认为 这是在这个任务上真正的希望
It's very hard to find out what people can do.
很难说人们可以做什么
So, here is what the data looks like. This is a part of Toronto.
这里是数据的样子 这是多伦多的一部分
If you know Toronto, you can tell that by the angle of the roads.
如果你了解多伦多 你可以通过道路的角度来判断
And, above the image of the part of Toronto, I put two patches extracted from
在多伦多照片上方 我放了从图片中提取的两个分块
that image. And if you look at those patches, you can
如果你看到那些分块 你可以
see it's not trivial to tell which the road pixels are.
知道很难去判断这是哪条路
On the right, is the output of [UNKNOWN] system.
在右边 这是[UNKNOWN]系统的输出
Green is correctly identified pixels of road, and red means things that his system
绿色是被正确识别出来的道路 红色代表系统
thought might be road, but actually aren't.
认为可能是路 但是实际上不是
Actually that thing is a parking lot but you can see why he might have thought it
事实上 那是一个停车场 但是可以看到为什么它可能认为
was a road.
是一条路 翻译 Naiding Zhou